http://www.bgtm.org/index.php/privacy-policy

Take Action
1-844-424-3577 (GCHELPS) Toll Free  |  Contact Us
AboutAbout
UsOur Core ValuesOur VisionHow We've GrownOur StoryOur LeadershipOur PeopleAccreditationsLocationsQuality ImprovementEvidence-Based Practices2017 Outcome HighlightsWhat We MeasureClient Rights and ResponsibilitiesCode of EthicsPrivacy Practices-HIPAAHMIS Privacy and Security NoticeGrievance ProcedureTitle VI/ADA Complaint FormWe Want Your FeedbackDiversity, Equity & InclusionGC Indirect Costs PolicyServices by ProgramAdmissions/Insurance Information24 Hour Specialized CareGeneral Mental HealthAutismAutismAutism Camp ProgramAutism Education ProgramAutism Residential ProgramAutism Respite ProgramCounseling ServicesIndividual, Family and Group CounselingCrisis ServicesEmergency SheltersCrisis Support for Women & ChildrenHomeless Youth ServicesOzark Foothills Child Advocacy CenterEducationOur ApproachOur CurriculumOur SchoolsAdmissionsFoster Care ServicesFoster ParentingTherapeutic Foster CareFoster Parent Training/LicensingFostering FuturesFoster Care Case ManagementHome & Community BasedHome Visiting – Healthy Families America®EAISONLearn, Grow, ThriveIntensive In-Home ServicesIn-Home Family SupportAftercare ProgramIntensive Family Intervention ServicesIntensive Family Reunification ServicesIntensive In-Home ServicesTransitional Youth ServicesImpact Us ProgramScattered Sites Apartment LivingTransitional Living Group HomesFoster Care Case ManagementIndividual, Family and Group CounselingPsychological ServicesStudent Support ServicesSupervised VisitationTherapeutic Mentoring Intensive Outpatient Program (IOP)Parenting SupportHome Visiting – Healthy Families America®EAISONLearn, Grow, ThriveIntensive In-Home ServicesParent Education & TrainingPAUSE ParentingIncredible Years ProgramParent Aide ServicesSuper CurricularMeramec Adventure RanchExpressive ArtsVirtual Mental Health ServicesServices by NeedAdmissions/Insurance InformationAutismBehavioral IssuesCrisis Support for Women & ChildrenFamily SupportLearning & Intellectual ChallengesOlder YouthParentingSocial Interaction ChallengesTraumaImpactFamily StrengthCentral RegionEastern RegionNorthwestern RegionSouth Central RegionSoutheastern RegionSouthwestern RegionWestern RegionEventsFundraising & Donor EventsFamilies & Kids EventsTrainings & WorkshopsEvent E-Mail ListNewsNews ReleasesStoriesIn the NewsFAQsStatsWhite PaperBlogCareersCurrent
OpeningsNow Interviewing For …VolunteerDonateWays to GiveDonate NowEmergency FundFundraising & Donor EventsRecurring Gift ProgramMatching GiftsCampaign For The Path AheadSmart Gift PlanningStart An Online FundraiserJoin Our Mailing List!
Developed in conjunction with Joomla extensions.
About
About
Us
Our Core Values
Our Vision
How We've Grown
Our Story
Our Leadership
Therapeutic Mentoring
Intensive Outpatient Program (IOP)
Parenting Support
Home Visiting – Healthy Families America®
EAISON
Learn, Grow, Thrive
Intensive In-Home Services
Parent Education & Training
PAUSE Parenting
Incredible Years Program
Start An Online Fundraiser
Join Our Mailing List!
AboutAbout
UsOur Core ValuesOur VisionHow We've GrownOur StoryOur LeadershipOur PeopleAccreditationsLocationsQuality ImprovementEvidence-Based Practices2017 Outcome HighlightsWhat We MeasureClient Rights and ResponsibilitiesCode of EthicsPrivacy Practices-HIPAAHMIS Privacy and Security NoticeGrievance ProcedureTitle VI/ADA Complaint FormWe Want Your FeedbackDiversity, Equity & InclusionGC Indirect Costs PolicyServices by ProgramAdmissions/Insurance Information24 Hour Specialized CareGeneral Mental HealthAutismAutismAutism Camp ProgramAutism Education ProgramAutism Residential ProgramAutism Respite ProgramCounseling ServicesIndividual, Family and Group CounselingCrisis ServicesEmergency SheltersCrisis Support for Women & ChildrenHomeless Youth ServicesOzark Foothills Child Advocacy CenterEducationOur ApproachOur CurriculumOur SchoolsAdmissionsFoster Care ServicesFoster ParentingTherapeutic Foster CareFoster Parent Training/LicensingFostering FuturesFoster Care Case ManagementHome & Community BasedHome Visiting – Healthy Families America®EAISONLearn, Grow, ThriveIntensive In-Home ServicesIn-Home Family SupportAftercare ProgramIntensive Family Intervention ServicesIntensive Family Reunification ServicesIntensive In-Home ServicesTransitional Youth ServicesImpact Us ProgramScattered Sites Apartment LivingTransitional Living Group HomesFoster Care Case ManagementIndividual, Family and Group CounselingPsychological ServicesStudent Support ServicesSupervised VisitationTherapeutic Mentoring Intensive Outpatient Program (IOP)Parenting SupportHome Visiting – Healthy Families America®EAISONLearn, Grow, ThriveIntensive In-Home ServicesParent Education & TrainingPAUSE ParentingIncredible Years ProgramParent Aide ServicesSuper CurricularMeramec Adventure RanchExpressive ArtsVirtual Mental Health ServicesServices by NeedAdmissions/Insurance InformationAutismBehavioral IssuesCrisis Support for Women & ChildrenFamily SupportLearning & Intellectual ChallengesOlder YouthParentingSocial Interaction ChallengesTraumaImpactFamily StrengthCentral RegionEastern RegionNorthwestern RegionSouth Central RegionSoutheastern RegionSouthwestern RegionWestern RegionEventsFundraising & Donor EventsFamilies & Kids EventsTrainings & WorkshopsEvent E-Mail ListNewsNews ReleasesStoriesIn the NewsFAQsStatsWhite PaperBlogCareersCurrent
OpeningsNow Interviewing For …VolunteerDonateWays to GiveDonate NowEmergency FundFundraising & Donor EventsRecurring Gift ProgramMatching GiftsCampaign For The Path AheadSmart Gift PlanningStart An Online FundraiserJoin Our Mailing List!
Developed in conjunction with Joomla extensions.
Privacy Policy
Our Privacy and Security Policy
Our Privacy and Security Policy
Great Circle realizes that visitors to our site may be concerned about how we utilize the personal information they provide to us. This Privacy Policy addresses those concerns. This policy may be changed or updated from time to time. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:
Great Circle
Phil McQueen
Director of Information Resources
330 North Gore Ave
St. Louis, MO 63119
We are available to answer your questions and address your concerns.
Privacy
Great Circle respects the privacy of its online visitors. At our site, we do not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. Visitors are not required to register or provide information to us in order to view our site.
Great Circle only gathers personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, zip/postal codes, e-mail addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by a visitor. This information is used solely by Great Circle or other entities that are involved in the operation of this site for internal purposes. Personally identifiable information is only shared with third parties in special cases. The following describes ways in which your information may be disclosed.
When the person submitting the information authorizes us to share it.
When a user makes an online donation, information gathered such as credit card numbers and contact information is sent to our payment processing merchant.
When the law requires us, as when we have reason to believe it is necessary to bring legal action against someone who may be violating our policies.
Great Circle has no control over, or responsibility for, the data collection and use practices of third parties that process online donation credit card transactions.
Secure Credit Card Transactions
Great Circle cares about the safety and security of your online credit card transactions. Secure and trusted security measures, such as high grade encryption and the https security protocol, are utilized for all transactions conducted on the Great Circle site. This makes it difficult for anyone to intercept credit card information sent to us. Companies we work with to process credit card transactions also use encryption and security protocols.
Use of "Cookies" on the Great Circle Site
Visitors should be aware that non-personal information may be automatically collected at the Great Circle web site through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small text files used by a web site to recognize repeat visitors. If a visitor does not want information collected through the use of cookies, most browsers can be set to deny or accept the cookie feature. The Great Circle web site uses cookies to obtain non-personal information from its visitors to improve their online experience and to evaluate the usage of the site.
Discover Great Circle
About Us Our Story Our People Our Leadership Services by Program Services by Need Helpful Links
844-424-3577 (GCHELPS)
Facility Locations330 North Gore AvenueSaint Louis, Missouri63119
Connect With Us
Affiliations, Certifications & Partners
© 2018 Great Circle. All Rights Reserved. | Privacy Policy
